[
  { "question": "1+1", "wrongAnswers": [1, 3, 4], "rightAns": 2 },
  { "question": "1+2", "wrongAnswers": [2, 4, 1], "rightAns": 3 },
  { "question": "2+5", "wrongAnswers": [6, 8, 3], "rightAns": 7 },
  { "question": "5+5", "wrongAnswers": [15, 0, 8], "rightAns": 10 },
  { "question": "7+2", "wrongAnswers": [8, 5, 6], "rightAns": 9 },
  { "question": "3+2", "wrongAnswers": [1, 4, 6], "rightAns": 5 },
  { "question": "7-3", "wrongAnswers": [10, 5, 3], "rightAns": 4 },
  { "question": "6-5", "wrongAnswers": [2, 10, 4], "rightAns": 1 },
  { "question": "3-3", "wrongAnswers": [1, 3, 6], "rightAns": 0 },
  { "question": "9-5", "wrongAnswers": [5, 7, 6], "rightAns": 4 }
]
